sklz.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**SECURITY AND PRIVACY**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

PRO PERFORMANCE SPORTS, LLC, a California limited liability company d/b/a SKLZ ("SKLZ", "we", or "us") will always respect the privacy of our customers. We want to give the best customer service possible.  SKLZ provides this privacy policy (this "Policy") to inform you of the types of information we collect and how we use it. This Policy applies to customer information obtained in connection with SKLZ’ operations at or through our websites, our mobile sites, our social media presence, our mobile applications, and our physical locations. For purposes of this Policy, our websites, our mobile sites, our social media presence and our mobile applications are referred to collectively as, our "Sites." Emails, social media (defined below), online marketing campaigns and online internet-based advertising are collectively referred to as, our "Internet Marketing Channels."

By accessing or using any portion of the Sites, you acknowledge that this Policy is part of the terms of use of the Sites and you agree: (1) that we and Third Parties (defined below) may gather your personal information in a manner consistent with that set forth herein; (2) that, except for audits conducted of select Third Parties by an independent auditor (including, without limitation, those conducted in accordance with Payment Card Industry ["PCI"] standards), Third Parties gathering information in connection with the Sites and related services are solely responsible for their own privacy monitoring technologies, data collection methods, data distribution or sharing practices, data handling, data security, privacy policies, and opt-out policies and procedures ("Privacy and Data Security Policies"); and (3) to be bound by all of the terms and conditions contained herein. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use the Sites.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

With the goal and intention of providing you products and services, and of improving your overall experience, we receive, collect and store information in a variety of ways, including when you visit our Sites or provide information to us. We may also collect information when you: (1) open an account with us; (2) utilize our services; (3) make a purchase; (4) contact us via any customer service method; (5) submit any user-generated content (via our Sites or otherwise); (6) participate in customer research, surveys, sweepstakes or promotions; or (7) otherwise communicate information to us.  Some of the information you provide is personal information. Examples of this information may be any of the following: your name, e-mail address, personal or business address, personal or business phone number, credit card information, personal and/or business demographic information, personal shopping, contact preferences, and personal and/or professional opinions.

We may also receive, collect and store "Automated Information" through Cookies (as defined below) and other related automated means.  Automated Information enables the tailoring of advertisements and offers specifically for you. In addition to such tailoring, we are interested in Automated Information to ensure that our mobile and/or online presence operates properly and efficiently for you and for your individual customer experience, to evaluate the use and benefit of such presence, and to support our Sites and our Internet Marketing Channels.

Functionality on the Sites (whether via cookies, your browser, browser settings or otherwise) may permit interactions between the Sites and third party social media websites (e.g. facebook, twitter, etc.) (each and collectively, "Social Media"). When you, or your browser, interact with Social Media, that information may become public and/or known to us and Social Media. One of the ways you may interact with Social Media is when you "like" a product or other content, "share" a product or other content, or comment on a product or other content. By you, your computer, or your browser taking such an action, you authorize us to share, access, and/or publish information about your activity in connection with the Sites and our services (such as "likes" and comments), and to access your Social Media information

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a small amount of data sent from our server and stored on your computer's hard drive.

COOKIES THAT ARE STRICTLY NECESSARY FOR THE OPERATION OF THE SITE

Some of the cookies we use are essential for parts of the Sites to operate and are already set. These are strictly necessary for the sale of products requested by you and without them the Sites cannot operate as intended.

OTHER USES OF COOKIES (WHERE THE USER HAS CONSENTED TO SUCH USE)

Where you consent to us doing so, we also use cookies and other such devices to compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our Sites and to help us improve the structure of our Sites (we cannot identify you personally in this way). We use cookies and other such devices to allow us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements on the Sites, to determine how frequently particular such pages and advertisements are visited, to determine the most popular areas of the Site and generally in order to monitor usage of the Sites.

Where you consent to us doing so, we may also use cookies and other such devices to:

  * to allow you to carry information across pages of our Sites and avoid having to re-enter information;
  * within registration to allow you to access stored information;
  * to help us recognize you as a unique visitor when you return to our Sites and to allow us to tailor content or advertisements to match your preferred interests or to avoid showing you the same adverts repeatedly;
  * speed up searches; and/or within research surveys to ensure you are not invited to complete a questionnaire too often or after you have already done so. 

**BROWSER SETTINGS**

Most internet browsers are automatically set up to accept cookies, but you can set your browser to refuse a cookie or ask your browser to show you where a cookie has been set up. Certain services are only activated by the presence of a cookie and, if you choose to refuse cookies, particular features of this Site may not be available to you.

Find out how to disable/enable cookies by clicking on the "Manage Cookies" section of the Interactive Advertising Bureau UK Site on the following link http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

We may use Adobe Flash Player to display video or image content. It may not possible to block or restrict flash cookies using your browser settings. However information on how to control flash player privacy and security settings is available from the Adobe Site at: http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security.

**SHARING OF THE INFORMATION  **

SKLZ uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and to better understand our audience's demographics.  Other than as indicated within this Policy, we do not sell, trade or rent your information to others. We and our service partners use your information to operate or repair our Sites and to deliver our services. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for products purchased on the Sites, and release your address information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered.

We may also be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personal information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose such information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena or warrant, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in attempting to identify those who use our services for illegal activities or who may otherwise be in violation of applicable law. We reserve the right to use, disclose, or share such information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding activities that we in good faith believe to be illegal or unlawful (whether criminally or civilly unlawful), suspected fraud, potential or actual violations of our Sites Terms of Use, and/or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or entity.

**SECURITY POLICY**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We use 128-bit SSL Encryption to encrypt important information, such as your credit card data, in an effort to prevent unauthorized access during transmission of your orders over the Internet. We incorporate standard industry practices internally and with our service providers suitable to the degree of sensitivity of the information involved to maintain the security of your personal information and to avoid its disclosure except as described in this Policy. Your personal information may also be protected by the password you created when you register at one of our Sites where this feature is offered. The confidentiality of any password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by following the instructions at the Site where you registered.

Although we use our best efforts to assure that your data remains secure when maintained by us, security during Internet transmissions cannot be assured. We limit access to personal data only to those SKLZ employees or agents with a specific need to access or retrieve this information. We store data on multiple service systems, in controlled, secure environments.

**PCI OVERVIEW**

The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) is a security standard which at Tier 1 Certification and compliance ensures unbeatable security and protection of sensitive customer information including credit cards.

The requirements for Tier 1 Certification include:

  * Security management policies;
  * Security policies;
  * Security procedures;
  * Network architecture;
  * Software design;
  * Critical Protective Measures.

Sites go through a rigorous INDEPENDENT audit and significant investment to attain Tier 1 PCI DSS certification. The purpose is to ensure that their customers' data is as safe as possible when they purchase products online.

Venda is the only global website provider to provide enterprise wide PCI DSS Tier 1 Certification. Visit www.venda.com for more information.

**VERIFIED BY VISA OVERVIEW**

Verified by Visa, also known as 3-D Secure, is an extra level of security developed by Visa and MasterCard to improve the security of payments and transactions offered to customers over the Internet. When you initiate a transaction using one of these card issuers you will be redirected to the website of your card-issuing bank to authorize the transaction. You will have to enter your password, or create one if you don’t already have one, which will then redirect you back to our site to complete your order. If you are creating a password, you can then use this password on any other site that uses 3-D Secure technology. Please note: this password is separate from the one you use to log in to our site.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Personal information and/or non-personal information may be gathered by Social Media, analytics services or other third party vendors or service providers (referred to herein as "Third Parties" collectively, or "Third Party" singularly"). Third Parties may monitor the Sites and/or their own websites for the purpose of gathering Sites traffic, statistics, advertisements, "click-throughs" and/or other activities, and such Third Parties may use cookies, web beacons, and other monitoring technologies to compile statistics and information about users, and/or to associate non-personally identifiable information with personal information.

Except for as otherwise provided within this Policy, we do not control Third Parties’ privacy and data security policies. Third Parties have their own privacy and data security policies. We recommend that you consult and familiarize yourself with such policies. However, we undertake no responsibility for or on behalf of such Third Parties’ compliance with or accuracy of their own policies.

**MINORS**

Our Sites are "general audience" websites and not geared toward children. In order to protect the privacy of children, our Sites do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 without express parental consent. If you are a parent or guardian and think we have unauthorized information about your child who is under the age of 13, please use the "Contact Customer Service" link below.

**YOUR CONSENT**

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by SKLZ. If we decide to change our Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
